[Music]
take good baby of this day time how are
you
all once again we take this opportunity
to thank each and every one of you and
all of you collectively for allowing
this transmission to occur through this
Gateway and in this manner and at this
time once again each and every time such
an interaction is allowed and co-created
by you it allows our civilization to
experience through each and every one of
you all the different perspectives that
are possible within creation and this
expands our understanding of the
infinite and so we thank you for this
opportunity and this gift we would like
to begin this transmission this day of
your time with the concept of gravity
this may at first sound somewhat as you
say
scientific But please understand that it
is also the science of the spirit the
science of the soul the science of
Consciousness
itself
gravity what is
it many of your scientists have been
pondering this idea for quite some
time many of your scientists are getting
close to understanding it in its most
fundamental interpretation
we have discussed with many of you over
the course of the time that we have been
transmitting to you that everything in
reality everything in your creation is
the product of vibration resonance
frequency Whatever frequency you give up
is the reality that is reflected back in
a sense in the most general
terms but the idea is that of course the
one the all that is whatever you wish to
call it
has its own signature vibration the
frequency that represents the Oneness of
all that is all things together and we
might wish to label that for the
purposes of this illustration as the
prime
resonance gravity can be understood as
the tendency of all
things to match the frequency of the
Prime resonance to gravitate toward that
frequency to gravitate toward the idea
of becoming one with all that is to be
attracted to the Oneness to join
together to integrate to merge as
closely as is possible for discrete
object for each object has its own
vibration its own signature frequency by
which you can recognize it its own
vibration and resonance that defines
every object but the tendency of every
object is to gravitate toward the prime
frequency and thus this is represented
or Illustrated or
demonstrated by the gravitic
attraction
toward all
things in understanding
this you can also know that movement all
movement whether it be the idea of the
movement you consider to be normal
moving from place to place or levitation
or teleportation the instantaneous
appearing movement from one place to
another without intervening travel all
these are the product of manipulation of
the vibrations of discrete objects so
that they are made to be more or
less more or
less in their tendency to gravitate
toward or away from the prime Resonance
of all that
is in in getting them to move away from
that frequency you will get them to move
away from anything that represents that
attraction such as mass a planet a star
what have
you by increasing that frequency toward
the prime resonance it will move toward
that mass the planet the star what have
you fundamentally this is all it is is
increasing its harmonic resonance with
the prime Resonance of the infinite of
the creation of the
one now this at first may not
necessarily seem to have a day-to-day
application to you but the more your
minds open up to seeing the concept of
vibration and resonance and frequency in
different ways the more you Ponder these
things and let them run around through
your brain
circuitry one day you will find as
things accelerate and things change and
you'll learn to see things from
different perspectives that these little
balls of information will suddenly fall
into a sloth click and certain things
will make sense that did not make sense
before many of the things that we share
with your people are simply seeds that
you allow us to plant that you plant
together with us in your Consciousness
that are not necessarily meant to bloom
right now but with the appropriate
amount of water sunlight and air so to
speak metaphorically speaking they will
one day all of a sudden burst forth from
their seed tasing
Sprout grow bloom Thrive and create a
garden of new understanding New
Perspective new thought and of
course a new
reality since your reality comes from
your ideas of reality so new ideas new
reality New Perspective new reality new
experience now paradoxically and you
know how much we love paradox
the less gravity you give to a situation
the more you lighten it
up then the more quickly you will be
capable of seeing and understanding this
relationship of vibrations of frequency
of resonances and understand yourself in
relationship to them and your life and
your circumstances and your situations
in relationship to the frequencies that
stem from your ideas perspectives fears
Joys doubts hesitations angers what have
you and the more you'll begin to
understand reality experience as an
orchestration of
frequencies a Discord or harmonic
expression of frequency
interaction a series of songs a
symphony of
experience let it all just sink
in you will begin to hear and see more
every day what we mean by these ideas as
they translate into your language it
does not matter if you understand it now
it does not matter if you think you
understand it now there will be
circumstances and situations wherein
many of the things that have been shared
not only by us but by others and among
yourselves for you are not without
wisdom all these things are coming
together with their own kind of
gravity and as they reach that that
critical MTH one day there will be a new
world in the place of the one you have
now in a sense all of the matter will be
replaced by other
matters and the things that matter now
will not matter
then we thank you for allowing us to
bring this matter to your
attention and in return for the gift
that you are giving our civilization in
allowing us to interact with you I ask
in return in what way may I be of
service to you
now you and then you number two do you
know who you are all right number one
good
day I have a question about
um Vanity Vanity flattery yes I was uh
listening to a tape of uh Barbara mariac
who talks about the pleadians and it
could have been Barbara I don't think it
was a pleadians but she would she said
something about don't don't ever fall
for
flattery and then a generalization that
has some degree of validity but it is a
generalization what came to mind was
that story you told us about happy Fox
and sad Fox yes happy Fox and sad Fox
yes well I never got really any moral
out of that is that got something to do
with it in do that's exactly at least
from one perspective the
moral the idea
that happy Fox was just being who he
was the idea that sad fox in attempting
to get happy Fox to aisee who he was for
being happy to make himself something
more than he
was and then when happy Fox bought into
that flattery is when happy Fox died and
was no longer in existence as the true
happy Fox as himself do you understand
that yeah therefore it is that when you
accept information about
yourself not that you cannot recognize
all of you that you are beautiful and
you are special and you are wondrous and
you are unique not that you cannot
recognize that but when in your terms
you allow it to go to your head when it
becomes the sole purpose for the
communication is to Simply embellish
upon yourself those ideas of name and
place and that's all you become then the
real you in a sense has died has
vanished and you're really not there
anymore you're nothing but a shell of
your former self do you follow yeah
that's I guess what was the rest of the
question was like how that applies to
spirituality and it applies to anything
you just you just answered that whole
time does that help yeah do you have
another um two words for me two words
the relationship game I like play I like
playing that with you oh all right
you here are your two words at this
time
Blossom and
sulfur okay I I'll I'll get back to you
on that one oh well yellow yellow thank
you thank you sorry you see it is easy
to connect things that seem unrelated if
you just take a moment to let
inspiration
inre with you now you can invent of
course your own words as well that is
the idea of association game now
sometimes you can play the game in both
directions you can see how
few other Concepts or words you can come
up with to make a bridge or a link
between the two that you are originally
given and on the other end you can see
how many who can come up with the most
who can take the longest to make the
link narrowly avoiding making the link
that is another way to play the game and
that will also stretch imagination
muscle you follow yeah okay I have one
for you oh all right map yes and point
seta yes well map points to things Point
set it starts with
points there you go thank you does that
help you yes songs of Joy all right and
for us as well thank you now next time
perhaps we will play the game with you
the other way and we will take turns
seeing how long we can avoid making a
connection the point of playing the game
that way is to understand in actual
fact it is more difficult to avoid
making a connection than to immediately
find one because all things are
connected do you
follow all right thank
you and to you as
well number good evening B and you good
day um last couple of times I've been
trying to guess at what might happen
December 2000 yes I know you like
playing that game yes that that's my
game so I have a new guest are you
having a good time I am thank you right
thank you I have a new guest uh is what
now first of all before you continue
yeah it is not so specifically tied to a
particular date we are simply referring
to what most of the people on your
planet are talking about about the kinds
of things that will occur within certain
Windows of times most likely between
your present day and your year of 2013
that will represent certain kinds of
accelerations and certain kinds of
changes on your planet and simply we
reinforce that for the most part none of
you have actually really guessed some of
the more profound things that will
actually occur this is what we are
talking about you don't necessarily have
to pin it down to a particular date
because there might be some fluctuation
in that but by all means do share yourk
yes okay um is it going to be that uh
well before you say
anything because we like playing with
you
too let me put an idea out for you okay
by all means do not allow us in any way
shape or
form to inhibit your willingness to play
this guessing
gang however I wish to add one more
factor to this idea that may give a
little bit of edge or spice to your game
as your humans put
it in that we have told you that there
are certain things that will unfold that
none of you have been capable of
guessing do you not imagine or suppose
that there might actually be a reason
and a value in why that would be and
that to actually guess them might be
contrary to your best
interest yes that's sort of part of my
guess tonight I see then maybe you're on
the right
track proceed
okay um if it was the case where you
said it was it was sort of being
prevented uh because it wouldn't be in
our best interest what would be
preventing us would be the collective
unconscious would in some senses yes so
I'm wondering is what's going to happen
happen is the collective consciousness
of the planet will become the
unconscious will become
conscious yes but that's a
given that is automatic that's what's
happening that is what is going on that
is creating the acceleration and the
change is that what you have created to
be the unconscious is becoming conscious
and you're integrating as a single
Consciousness what we were referring to
are some of the specific kinds of ways
in which that integration will manifest
themselves as singular events on your
planet in that many people have guessed
this or that that will be representative
as singular events to represent this
blending and acceleration and going into
a new age of awareness that your
unconscious is becoming more conscious
is simply part of the mechanism and
that's automatically well one event that
would do that would be a mass withdrawal
of spirit from the physical yes but many
of you have guessed that that's what
might happen and we have said that the
events that we are talking about no one
has guessed
okay uh uh let me move on to something
else um last time when um Pamela was
talking about the woman that we are
helping who whose children are being
abused by a cult and you wouldn't talk
about it and you said but you did say
that you are there for her you speaking
spe specifically that pamel at the
moment yes um and I assume you're there
for all of us that are helping her yes
um I was wondering what you mean by
there for us what in what sense are you
there for I will give you one level of
it remember that many of the strongest
interactions that we and other beings
such as ourselves and or Spirit beings
have with many humans is in what you
call the dream
space in many dream interactions we are
having already what you consider to be
on ongoing contact conversation
communication
interaction in so far as you are willing
many of you to stretch out in your dream
state to see what it is you can do about
changing your physical reality once you
reconnect to it in what you call your
waking State we are there with you in
those dream states discussing planning
orienting teaching reflecting learning
and sharing the Myriad of ideas that can
be applied into your physical reality
that you think is best to apply for the
purpose of what is best for all
concerned and on that level at least
that is one way we are there for
you okay but when you wake up in your
physical reality in that many of you
have still understood this physical
reality game on earth to be one that
requires a bit of random unknown in
order to function in the way you really
prefer it to then many of you will
simply empirically forget many of those
conversations consciously you will push
them into a level of yourself that you
typically call the subconscious so that
it can run on automatic and simply allow
you to direct yourself towards certain
events in a spontaneous and creative way
so that it simply doesn't become robotic
or automatic in terms of how you fulfill
what it is we have discussed in the
etheric dream state realm because then
you allow yourself the spontaneity of
creation as to how to transform these
things and it simply isn't the roope
practice of Simply repeating the steps
we have talked about because there will
always be a new Factor when you are
connected to a different reality such as
physical life there will always be the
spontaneous momentto moment creation
that you have to take into account and
so in order to do that in the way that
is best you allow yourself to forget
some of the things that we have
discussed not that you will not
Implement them but you will Implement
them according to how it is appropriate
for the physical reality you have
reconnected to does that make sense to
you yes does that answer your question
yes I have more yeah it's all right I
figured that was the case um when you
say is there are there more alien groups
than just yours that are helping yes yes
yes yes can you name any of them well
many of them you know or some of them
you know in the sense of what you
typically call the pleadians and the
Orion and the serious group there are
several and there are some we cannot
name at this time but those groups some
of those groups are specifically helping
this woman with this situation some
individual members in some of those
groups are specifically helping the
woman you are referring to and many
other people on your planet with regard
to this particular issue which is a very
important issue on your planet at this
time since it is time to break the chain
on your planet of those situations and
circumstances that has created much of
the dysfunctionality in many of the
adults or the so-called adults that
exist on your planet at this time and so
that situ are you referring specifically
to pedophilia or forms of what you
typically call abuse all forms of what
you typically call the devaluation of
the Soul okay and um are there is there
also Angelic Health involved yes but
that is not what we would call an
extraterrestrial being right in the way
you classically mean it and what do you
what what how what is an angel and how
does it differ from the Angelic
Consciousness is as we refer to it the
level of Consciousness that is the first
differ iation from the one it is the
first level of split off from the
undifferentiated whole of all that is
the first reflection the first moment of
awareness just to speak linearly that
what you call God or all that is had
that it was self-aware caused a
reflection in order to see itself as
self-aware that automatically implies a
segregation a separation a
self-reflection that self-reflection Bec
because God is God created
differentiated Consciousness that first
split-off reflective differentiated
Consciousness is what you call Angelic
Consciousness so to put it colloquially
the angels are the first level down from
the one the first differentiation of the
one into the many then from there it
goes down down down into different
levels of oversold Consciousness and
into differentiated personality
structure consciousnesses such as
spirits and souls and so forth we are
skipping a few levels but you get the
point yes does that help you yes I
wonder you earlier at at some point some
months ago you mentioned a person that
would come along in this month December
that would
embody uh aspects of lady d and Mother
Teresa and some of us who know this
woman in question are wondering if you
referring specifically to her you have
made a misinterpretation all right what
we are saying is not that there cannot
be specific embodiments that might
reflect more or less the qualities you
are referring to but that the idea of
the passing of those individuals
requires now the embodiment of those
qualities in all of
you they have now in a sense less the
Physical Realm by showing you the kinds
of things that need to be done so that
in leaving you are forced to take those
qualities into your own heart and
express them in your own ways rather
than simply letting them do it for
you it is the time of self-
responsibility self-action and this is
one of the reasons why many of those
that act as symbols and Reflections are
going to leave so that it is up to you
to embody those Concepts and qualities
within yourself and become your own
version of them so to speak okay does
that make sense to you it does and I'd
like to just I'd like to tell you that
the woman in question is here tonight
I'm just wondering if she wants to ask
qu a question of you now or later well
you may Wonder All You Wish but probably
you will get an answer if you ask would
you would like to ask the Char question
now or later all right a little later
thank you thank you you good
day good evening all right good day Ju
Ju Just to follow up on the last
question yes
is there not someone that is going to
check out in the month of December there
always will be that has that has had as
much impact as Diana and Mother Teresa
not so much in December but we will not
name names but look for it within the
first three months of the New Year okay
so it's uh very nice to be here I really
want to thank you for um a suggestion
you made a few months ago regarding
visiting Sydney
Australia I did do that all right
and I had what you have described in the
past as an ecstatic explosion
congratulations coincidences that's
synchronicity one of which took me off
to Melbourne all right
and how did your life unfold from there
well moving from the specific to the
general if you wish um coming back to
Melbourne in 1 second I went up to A's
rock or A's rock yeah it's understood
and sleeping outside that just
coincidentally again happened to be a
full moon uh with a group of others and
sleeping outside and I'm aware of the
significance of of A's Rock and and the
power that it generates etc etc but I I
woke up at about 3:30 in the morning
everybody was about to wake up at 4:00
a.m. anyway but I woke up and I was abs
and this has happened once before in New
Mexico as well well where I sat up in my
sleeping bag looked up at the sky and
absolutely am convinced that I felt uh
as well as saw uh something of a uh
exceptionally unusual nature all right
and so well I was just wondering aside
from the fact that I know that it was
real uh why I'm having so so much
trouble remembering
it many of those kinds of incidents are
not for surface remembering they are for
were deep
impacting if you look into the feelings
you had and the energy you felt during
that reflection or exchange that is the
reason why those things happen to awaken
those energies within you and all else
the surface expression of it in a sense
is secondary and why it is pushed aside
because it is also known by simple
observation on your planet
that most of your people no offense over
time have had I'll use the word a
tendency just to be light on you a
tendency to focus on the surface and
completely lose the meaning this is one
of the reasons why the surface is taken
away and you are only left with the
feeling so that you are forced to relate
to the Deeper Self if you're going to
relate to the incident at all and you
cannot just lock on to the surface
effect
any longer you follow that
logic that's
why both because you don't want to
remember that you want to understand who
you are and it is getting in touch with
that feeling that will help you do that
both because you don't want to remember
it for that reason and because in
knowing that you don't want to remember
it you are then assisted in not
remembering the surface idea by those
with whom you
interact because they understand that
that's the point and the understand that
getting in touch with the deeper feeling
and the deeper energy is what you
prefer does that help
you along the same lines Dad I'm having
trouble
remembering I'm having trouble
remembering yes what my joy
is oh all right is that really so
difficult well forgetting it seems to be
easy oh all right well at least you can
do that well you have excelled and
succeeded brilliantly and marvelously at
forgetting what your joy is that should
make you happy to know that you're doing
that so perfectly you can always use the
Paradox of something to put you back in
touch with it just to let you know that
before we move on did you follow that
idea absolutely that's why I raised it
like that all right thank you now the
second point is in that you did raise it
like that you do know what you're doing
you always know what you're doing you
haven't forgotten it's not really
difficult it may simply be that you have
wrapped it in a definition that might
really not do it justice or might really
be more than it needs to be bring things
as
that when it comes to following your
highest Joy you simply simply
begin simply begin at any moment with
looking at all the options available to
you at any given moment and simply pick
the one and act upon the one out of all
the things that you are capable of doing
at any given moment that contains out of
those things the highest Joy it doesn't
have to be the highest Joy you will ever
imagine in your life at that moment but
simply the one that contains the most
excitement out of all the things you're
aware of at that moment is enough to
begin the process
rolling that's all it takes that's why
it really is impossible to forget or
lose your joy because all you have to do
is simply say well I have a b and C to
choose from right now is a more exciting
is B more exciting is C more exciting
which
one act on the one that contains the
highest excitement that you have the
highest degree of ability to do
something about that's all you have to
do and that is what will lead you to the
next most exciting circumstance and the
next opportunity to choose and the next
opportunity to choose because all
excitement is connected because
excitement is your translation of your
true inner harmonic
frequency does this make sense to you
well yes no maybe Melbourne Melbourne
Australia yes I I end up there under
exceptionally coincidental circumstances
yeah synchronistic I meet someone from a
company that I've been dying to get into
and the next not literally We Trust yeah
yeah no no no and then the next thing I
find myself I'm at his house two
evenings later having dinner with his
family and your point is
what am I what what
um
yes am I con
yes what am I supposed to remember about
my excitement with regards to these
events these wonderful events occurred
nothing but I'm doing nothing nothing
you are supposed to enjoy them as they
unfold that's it you're supposed to live
your life and enjoy what the
synchronicity of following your
excitement brings you without
expectation that it's supposed to come
to some particular fruition or be
remembered in some particular way you're
supposed to live your life not ponder it
but do what whatever takes you in the
next moment whatever excites you in the
next moment it isn't nothing a
option is that the most exciting thing
lately all right then that's it but even
then you're not really doing nothing
you're doing something you're making a
choice is is the point choice is all you
have choice is all there is choose thou
as it says in some of your scriptures
that's it choose thou if you choose what
passes for nothing because it excites
you more than anything else you are
being honest with yourself if you're
choosing nothing not because it is the
most exciting but simply because you're
not willing to believe that you can act
on what really would be more exciting
then you're being dishonest with
yourself and it's as simple as that make
youro accordingly well I thank you for
pointing me in the direction initially
of Australia is this making any sense to
you or are you confused well I have to
thank myself for for following my
instincts Oh by all means do so yes but
uh but I really do uh acknowledge that
you had a co-creation participation role
in that of course all right thank you
but the point is is what we are saying
now making sense to you no thank you for
your
honesty you you have a particular
assumption or a particular expectational
definition that is getting in the way of
clarity here you are assuming that
something has to be recognized or
understood or remembered or seen in a
particular light and that's what's
confusing
it you have all of you this goes for all
of you but I'm talking to you you
have no other
reason for being than just
being you don't need a reason to be who
you are because you are who you
are whatever way you choose to express
what it means to be who you are is your
choice there is no expectation upon you
from anywhere any when anyone anything
to do or be or know or say or think or
remember or anything anything
else being whoever it is you deem you
are living your life the way you choose
to that's your only purpose your only
Mission your only
goal that's it how you choose to do that
is up to your free
will does that make any more sense yes
it does thank you very much drop the
expectations drop the assumption that it
has to be understood in a particular way
and you will have understanding because
understanding only comes with experience
and experience only comes with
living does that make some sense well
without appearing to be arrogant oh all
right is there anything you'd like to
know from me why there are many things
we would love to know from your species
and we have asked many questions of many
of you many times we do not assume that
we will understand the answers because
in many ways your Society is quite
unfathomable to
us but there are many things we would
like to know yes and we have asked many
questions many times about why your
species chooses to do this or chooses to
do that some of the things we understand
some of the things we don't the idea
really is however that whatever it is we
need to know about you we learn through
the interactions in whatever way shape
or form they come
we do not expect that they have to go a
particular way and we don't really make
an attempt to focus them into an
academic sort of structure to shall we
say extract from you empirical knowledge
that will then fit our tidy questions in
a tidy way that's not how we function
the things we want to know are
automatically a part of the reasons
simply for living our lives in the way
we do and choosing to interact with you
because it is our joy to automatically
wound up in our desire to Simply
interact with you because it is joyful
will come we simply already know all the
things we need to know that we don't
know
now did you follow that isn't the
majority of us sitting in this room
being very silly trying to take your
perspective and fit it into our quote
unquote unfathomable framework
yes and that we have always said for our
perspective is our perspective the idea
is if you choose to in our perspective
may be elements and
ideas that can be molded into your
perspective that may work for you in a
similar way that's the idea it is not in
that sense the adoption of our
perspective completely it is the
understanding that you have different
perspectives and the understanding that
you can choose what perspective you
prefer and in so doing then in your own
way will you function in the same joyful
methodology that we do with our
perspective some of our perspectives may
be very similar some of our perspectives
may not the whole point is that if you
simply know what's yours and live the
perspective that is truthfully you then
in that way you will be living the same
way we are even if it isn't specifically
similar does that make sense always a
pleasure to be here and for us
absolutely as well to interact with all
of you down
there you and then you number one number
two do you know who you are all right
number one female good day hi
Bashar oh I wanted to ask you about an
experience I had recently under hypnosis
under hypnosis yes where I came into uh
contact with some beings while I was
staring down at Earth Earth yes
panicking panicking about going there
and um about going where to Earth to
Earth yes and I got a lot of answers uh
from myself or through these beings it
was kind of wishy-washy as to where I
was getting the answers oh all right
wishy washy but it it concerned what I
was doing here and you just talked about
not having anything we're supposed to do
but yet I got from these beings and I
don't know if it was because that's what
I wanted um kind of reminding me what I
was supposed to do yes I understand what
you are referring to there is no
contradiction listen to it this
way each and every one of you as a
Consciousness has chosen to
personify an aspect of the Consciousness
that you are as a physical being are you
with me so far in personifying shall we
say in
crystallizing in
solidifying if you will an aspect of
your total Consciousness as a physical
human
person you
imbue by
definition in that
personification a frequency that is
representative of what
experience both General and sometimes
specific the cre ation of that person is
for therefore that vibration will always
key to the things in that reality or of
that reality that will trigger and
amplify and resonate with the structure
with the frequency of that
personification and that can in some
sense represent the things you are
supposed to do but in that context all
that is meant by that
is that these are things you yourself
have decided to explore in some manner
as a theme of why you projected your
Consciousness as a physical being in
this life therefore certain things will
resonate to you you will be attracted to
them you will find yourself drawn into
them and they will seem like missions
and purposes and the things you're
supposed to do because they are
representative they are representative
of the theme vibration that you have
decided to create this life for but how
you go about it in many ways is still up
to you walk down the hallway yes you may
have created that kind of a so-called
Destiny for this physical
personification of your Consciousness
but how you walk down the hallway how
many doors you look in what doors you
look in what the hallway is made out of
what the doors are made out of which way
they open which part of the hallway
you're walking on who's in the hallway
with you many of these things are the
product of what you call your free will
will and are representative of your
ability to choose based on your
excitement walk down the hallway you
will does that make sense to you yes
well at the end of it I felt very
confident and back on track so to speak
and and now I'm I'm beating myself s up
a little because oh all right is that
enjoyable no are you a
masochist sometimes oh all right
but but
I don't know I had so much trust at the
time that everything was going to play
out and everything is but again remember
believe that but I don't anymore
remember
remember remember I'll remind you okay
Paradox always here's the formula in its
entirety act on the highest Joy at any
given moment with zero expectation for
how it's going to unfold
zero that is what keeps you in the
center at the balance point if you say
well all right I'll act on my excitement
so that it will then play out this way
well you have set yourself
up because you don't necessarily know
that playing out that way is the best
way to be most representative of your
ultimate highest Joy you don't know that
so by insisting that that's the way it's
got to go you are short changing and
short circuiting
yourself you follow mhm by having that
as a key A Vision in a sense a marker a
guideline that's fine but if you make it
an expectation and an assumption that
it's got to happen that way will you
automatically contradict the spontaneity
of your creator Hood because at any
given moment everything could change you
may want it to change you may have
changed it and you will want to respond
appropriately to the automatic
simultaneous changes you won't want to
be stuck in a rut you won't want to be
fixed it's got to happen this way got to
happen that way no go with the flow
trust the flow trust the change as long
as you follow your joy you will know you
are on
track but don't have the Assumption or
expectation that your joy has to
solidify in some particular manner or
you're not getting the point of
spontaneous
creation being in the moment living in
the now
is what it's
about does that make any sense oh it
makes a lot of sense you see you have
enough structure in the general hallway
you have created you don't need any more
structure than that you're not going to
get out of the hallway that's what the
hallway is for the hallway is to give
you pay attention enough automatic
structure so that you will know you are
guided you don't need to impose any more
structure on yourself than you have
already imp osed by incarnating to begin
with I felt that structure very
intensely yes because many of you
reinforce it with your ideas about how
life is supposed to be lived and you
make that a very narrow tiny
claustrophobic hallway because you have
filled it like cholesterol in your veins
with so much structure that the passage
is now very narrow and tight and your
life blood your life energy cannot get
through
so open it up dissolve the structures
that you have imposed upon the only
structure you really
need drop the expectational structures
follow your joy respond in the moment as
best as you know how and you will find
your life will unfold much more
creatively much more abundantly much
more effortlessly and much more
joyfully okay I have to ask you about a
I hear the trepidation in your vibration
no it it's not that it's
okay we'll see no no no I believe you no
no no I don't want you to believe me I
want you to believe in yourself that's
the
point there's the big one yes you see
there's the trepidation we heard you
have to believe in yourself but what
does that mean is that really so
difficult if you really stop and think
about it it's actually the only thing
you can do yeah it is there is nothing
else to believe in there is nothing
else you are all that is in in your own
life that's it you are you the
individual you the individual you the
individual
are all that
is experiencing itself as a part of
itself but you are the whole of itself
experiencing itself as a part there's
the ultimate
Paradox so you are all that is within
your own reality
let us tell you a story that exists on
your
planet this story comes from what you
call one of your Indian
nations what many of you call Su laot
D and perhaps it can be used to
illustrate the
point the Creator called All of creation
together
and
said I want to hide
something so that humans will not find
it until they're
ready what I want to hide is the
realization that they create their own
reality the eagle said I will take it
and hide it on the
moon the Creator said no humans will one
day go to the moon and they will find it
there the salmon says I will take it and
I will hide it in the bottom of the sea
no says the Creator they will find it
there too the Buffalo says I will take
it and I will hide it in the Great
Plains no the Creator said one day they
will tear up the skin of the earth and
they will find it even
there then grandmother mole who
lives of the need for it to have to
happen in a certain way you will be
deluged with all forms of abundance but
again you trap Yourself by saying oh
goody then I'll let go so that I will be
Deluge and right back into the Trap you
go because you make it conditional yes
all right I'll let go and instantly in
the next breath you make it conditional
and haven't let go Letting Go means
letting
go Letting Go means in one moment you're
going oh I need that I need that I need
that happened this way I need it to
happen this way I do I do I do and in
the very next second
going what was I just talking about I
don't know oh I'm having a very good
time right now I don't know why but I
just am
oh no more thought of how it has to
happen no more thought of how it needs
to show itself just following your joy
acting on your joy and knowing knowing
and here's the the key
knowing to such a degree that you will
be supported that you don't even have to
think about it that it never has to
cross your mind I was there I was there
and I was experiencing that and what
what Chang what made you choose to leave
that's what
changed what made you choose to leave
that state now this does not have to be
a negative remember we have already
given you the stretching analogy and for
many of you that will be the reason to
change that state because you want to
stretch even
further so the idea and the Paradox and
the way to use the power of the Paradox
is to understand that if that is why you
did leave that state then leaving the
state is a part of the state and you
won't feel having left the state as
leaving the state
are you getting this Paradox at all I
don't think so listen
again if you understand that leaving the
state is a part of the state you won't
feel that you have left the state when
you
do if you know I'll put it in other
terms if you know that the reason you
have changed and gone into another state
is for the purpose of actually
ultimately expanding the state you were
in that you enjoyed then it will be all
right that you're in the state you're in
because you will see it as a part of the
expansion of that state and not an
opposition or an interruption to it and
when you know that you will feel no
difference between making the change and
having been in that state and it will
all then become the same vibration and
that's when you will allow it to have
the same effect that it did before
because you will not be making a
difference it's when you make the
difference it's when you say there is a
difference in feeling between this and
that it's when you label that this has
nothing to do with that that's what
makes the difference and that's what
makes you feel it as if it's different
and makes it manifest something other
than what is reflective of the state you
say you prefer is disining
in um I yes but I yes I yes right all
right um uh it still feels like very
external not internal why is that and
why is that we're
situations and why is
that do you remember what we defined
feelings as where do they come from
vibration where do feelings stem
from
louder definition
I know it feels like that but the only
reason it feels like that is because you
define it as
that you have to get in touch with the
fact that you're defining it as
different as less than as other than
right and when you define it as
different than less than other than you
feel that it is because it will
reinforce itself based on the definition
okay fear is the definition so fear is
the definition fear of what fear of lack
well the definition yes all right and so
you feel it that way right but but if
you know that the definition is only a
definition then why do you choose why
are you motivated to buy into that
definition as if it were real instead of
Simply recognizing that it's nothing but
a definition why are you motivated to
buy into it and make it
solid that's the next question question
once you say What's the definition
that's question number
one the next question is all right if
that's the definition fear of lack what
is my motivation for supporting that
definition and there in lies a very
critical key because we translated the
word support because you see what you're
doing is you you all of you
you are the source of abundance for your
death
definitions you are what Empower your
definitions to be real you are the
unlimited source of energy and abundance
to your definitions that you ask for
from the
universe is this making sense to
you yes it think of your definitions an
intellectual think of your definitions
as
people fear of lack is a person that's
his or her name nice to meet you fear of
lack fear of lack deres power from fear
of lack God fear of lack's God is
you you are supporting fear of lack you
are giving fear of lack abundance of
energy unlimited unconditional infinite
abundance and empowering fear of lack to
continue to be fear of
lack you are supplying to fear of lack
the kind and level of abundance you as a
person say you want to receive from your
God from the universe from creation from
the
infinite so in that you are supplying an
unlimited abundance to fear of lack
don't you simply see that you could
switch that abundance around to
something else and then you will
experience the abundance you are giving
to fear of lack as something different
perhaps Abundance of Joy
abundance of
abundance I can do that momentarily well
that's up to you and then if you decide
not to be in that moment in the next
moment ask yourself why and find out
what the motivation is and what the
definition is and you will be right back
into it again it's a self-perpetuating
idea and at every moment you have to
decide what do I believe why do I
believe it what am I getting out of
believing it do I prefer it yes or no
what would I prefer to believe then
believe in what you prefer okay uh and
if I could get into uh one other thing
all right on in the spirit of abundance
we will allow you one other thing okay
thank you um uh the um the ancient
language of your people yes um if you
are what I understand you're in you're
in a different dimensional plane but if
you are in what we would pered to be 300
years in our future and you are
descendants of us in the grave yes how
is it possible for you to have an
ancient language because the frequency
of our Dimension is faster than yours 10
times faster 300 years in the future
relatively speaking is actually 3,000
years of History to
us okay make S your civilization has
been around for 3,000 years to us yes
right to to you yes and uh how how long
in in that perspective of that 3,000
years as we would perceive it uh have
have you guys been not
communicating uh verbally or with a
physical language for about what you
would recognize as the last 300 years
300 of the 3,000 yes okay completely
completely non-verbal except when we may
choose to for a variety of artistic
reasons but there were incidents that
led up to a lot of levels of non-verbal
communication but absolutely nonverbal
about 300 years ago and was that uh was
that language a derivative of the
language used by any humans and the
Grays or was it a completely different
language no it is a combination of a
multitude of languages on your planet
but also given its own context and
syntax according to the understanding of
what it is were to
become okay is there any uh language
currently used on this planet uh or that
that has existed on this planet that
would be similar or that was a a kind of
a base language for what your language
started out as no it is an amalgamation
utterly and no other language on your
planet has ever been anything like
it and how did how did that language
come to be it was concocted and created
by the
graves by the graves rather so for us
and talk to us
oh but they don't they don't use verbal
communication do they no but they knew
we needed to for our development because
they wanted that aspect of our minds to
parallel human development and to see
how we would understand concept by
having an attendant language to go along
with it so that we would develop
similarly yet differently but similarly
to humans
okay it makes a difference and they knew
that if we didn't have one we would
develop more like them and that's not
what they wanted they were after a true
hybridization so they laid down the
telepathic grid and the syntax and
context telepathically but yet concocted
a madeup language to pin on that grid so
that we would have both worlds
intact and how does how does that
relates to uh to your communication with
the dolphins
not very strongly for that it is mostly
the idea of resonance Andor telepathic
contact since they are a completely
different species from
humans okay thank you thank you you good
day um I've been having good day good
day thank you sorry do not apologize I
have U been having a lot of problems
with my brain oh all right a lot of
challenges with your brain yes and I'm
very concerned about it all right what
Manner are these challenges making
themselves known well I'm very very very
forgetful what did you say forgetful
pardon
me I um I don't have are you sure it's
your
brain are you sure it's simply not your
desires your priorities I'm asking your
choices well I'm giving you hints what
do you
think um what kind of things do you
believe are forgetful about can you give
us an
example something from one of your daily
interactions that you believe represents
the forgetfulness you are referring
to well it's pretty random is the
problem it's really hard to pinpoint
well just give an example um I forget or
have you forgotten them all actually I
have oh all right well then you have
forgotten about your forget so perhaps
you could simply move on with your life
in that you don't remember that you are
forgetting and so everything is it's
fine but it it's pretty pretty apparent
to me when other people tell me about
things I such as what well conversations
and and um business uh have you delved
into yourself in a
self-examination modality to see if you
might have a motivation for forgetting
these
things I'll give you a hint if you want
i' like all right thank you I don't want
to over tax your forgetful brain no
offense
this is just a question I am not
suggesting this is the case you
understand yes this is just a
question might it have something to do
with feeling unmotivated in what you're
doing definitely because many times when
many
individual on your planet are
unmotivated on a very fundamental level
they could care less about anything else
or in fact actually more precisely they
couldn't care
less so it might be that you're
experiencing a
leakage a leakage of
demotivation if you are deeply feeling
unmotivated then that will begin to
bubble and percolate up to everything
else in your life and you will
ultimately say what am I doing anything
for none of this is worth doing so if
it's not worth doing it's certainly not
worth remembering
when you get down
deep and find the things that would
motivate you you will most likely find
it assuming that you have no actual
physical impairment which I do not
believe you do you will generally start
finding that you will remember the
things you really need to remember and
you will start remembering more things
when you are motivated to be who you
prefer to be because then your life will
be worth remembering
in some senses what you're telling
yourself is that your life isn't worth
remembering do you follow so do you have
any idea or any suggestion in your
imagination now this doesn't take memory
so don't worry you have any imaginary
ideas whatsoever about something that
would be more exciting that would be
more motivating that you could be doing
if you could do anything if you could do
anything other than what you're doing in
your life what would it be I'm try to
figure out oh no don't have to try you
don't have to try let's keep it simple
let's keep it as a
game do you and I know this is probably
going to scare you for me to ask it this
way do you
remember anything in childhood that
might have been a childhood
dream that might still be something you
would really love to do but perhaps
simply don't believe you can do in any
practical
way anything at all
I can't think of anything I can't
remember but I already told you it
doesn't take
memory I'm not making a oh all right
let's render it into its most basic
form I will ask you a question if I may
may I yes why thank you so very
much I am
honored why why did you attend this
interaction this day of your
time I broken Buton here but why did you
accept the invitation because I'm
open-minded and I I wanted to to hear
you
why um but actually I wanted to ask you
this
question so what you're saying is you
were excited you were motivated about
asking this question yeah well now that
wasn't so hard was it you see but what
you have done
and why at first it didn't seem as if
you could pull up
anything is that you have in some senses
paradoxically enough even though I
understand this was an important
question you wanted to ask you have
actually simultaneously rendered the
question not important enough to be
something to be excited about on its own
Merit and therein lies the difficulty
you are having you have been fed a diet
of definitions that says that certain
things are not worthy of being listed as
things that should be called worthy of
Merit or exciting or things to be
motivated
about are you
following all
right let me again put it in even more
pragmatic term I'll ask it the way most
humans ask it on your planet what do you
do for a
living I'm a salesperson so table
Network programing why
give me all the reasons why you are
doing what you're doing well it got me
to Colorado it gives me a very free
lifestyle it got you to Colorado yes it
gives you a free lifestyle yeah are you
somehow now I don't want to overstep my
bounds are you somehow suggesting that
something about a free lifestyle and
something about Colorado are somehow oh
shall I say it exciting to you yeah are
you somehow motivated by those Concepts
yeah oh
no why were those Concepts not worthy of
mentioning when I asked you what
motivates
you because I I'm motivated by many many
many things uh you just said I am
motivated by many many many things but
when I asked you for one you didn't come
up with any because they're not specific
enough so what do you see you are again
allowing them to become diffused because
you are defining them in such shall I
say a mushy way you are lumping them all
together into an undifferentiated pot
and somehow letting them all become
homogeneous instead of being in their
own right worthy of being called out as
valuable and exciting on their own Merit
instead of having to connect them to
something
else many humans on your planet get
themselves into trouble when they think
they need to do a certain thing in order
to do another thing you have just said
and I'm not trying to take this away
from you if it is truly something you
find exciting although you have
intimated you don't I'm not trying to
take your job away from you or tell you
to quit but the idea is that what you
have said in the way you have said
it implies that the only reason you have
it is because you think that's what you
need in order to have something else you
actually
want that's not
true that's just what you've been
taught let's do a little exercise shall
we
yeah and this exercise will
simultaneously help you stretch your
gray
matter all right
okay let's use your example being in
Colorado having a free lifestyle now
those are things that excite you yes I'm
just double cheing yes all right when
you think of them when you live them you
actually do find yourself becoming
excited yes yes all right just checking
can you can you name whether it makes
any
sense or not in the way you've been
taught to think of things as making
sense whether it seems silly or not in
the way you've been taught to think of
things as being silly I don't care can
you
think of any other
way to be in Colorado and have a free
lifestyle other than the way you're
doing
it can you name one other way it might
be possible to be in Colorado and have a
free lifestyle other than the way you're
doing it yes name it a a a sales job
with another company would would be good
a product that I can believe in believe
in and and get excited about and a
better energy all right new what's
stopping you from finding them actually
I think I have just recently all right
but are you getting the point well I
want to I am I think all right the point
is you are really far less limited than
you think with regard to the paths and
methodologies that are available to you
to allow you to actually have the
lifestyle you prefer you do not have to
necessarily chain yourself to something
that is not representative of your joy
in order to get something that you say
is in fact that's self-contradictory and
that's where you're having difficulty
because you see many of you are brought
up with this philosophy that the The end
justifies the means the end and the
means are one and the
same do you follow
yeah
so now don't stop there it may be that
right now this other sales job is the
most exciting thing you can imagine or
something that is far more exciting than
the sales job you're doing now but don't
stop there don't even limit yourself to
the idea that it has to be a sales job
unless sales jobs are something that
really excites you are they
I'm I'm not sure at this point I'm I'm
hoping this I'm going to take that as a
no now I understand the human capacity
for fooling yourself and preventing
yourself sometime from actually seeing
what does excite you sometimes something
that does excite you can actually be
denied by you as being exciting but in
this case I do not sense that's what's
happening so as a general rule of thumb
as you say when I ask the question does
that excite you and you say something to
the effect of I'm not sure that can
usually be taken as a solid
no because otherwise if it did excite
you the answer would be instantaneously
and immediately yes that's right any
hesitation at
all usually means some variation of
no you can use that as a general rule of
thumb do you follow me yes I do you see
how quickly you said yes yes thank you
is this helping you thank you very much
our love to you thank
you one two three number one do you know
who you are number two do you know who
you are number three do you know who you
number one good day good day Bashar I'm
having fun with Christmas again this
year all right it's very different all
right a very merry very different
Christmas to
different um how is it
different oh for the for the state that
I'm living in and the state of being you
mean the state of being yeah it's
different and the flow of things uh the
Christmas tree that I just picked out
today is different than right so
everything is different based on the
differences you have made within you
right all right and you're sensing that
now more profoundly than ever before by
comparison is that what you are
suggesting yeah and last year at
Christmas time last year I had a big 10
half chist tree and it was huge and
everything and I said at that time I
don't know what Christmas is going to be
like next year and now you do to be
different all right very good now I'm
here and it is all right thank you for
your self-fulfilling
prophecy right and it's perfectly fine
yes of course with it all right um I
want to talk about the Stars which stars
would those be two stars that are eyes
oh yes that we I mentioned last syus and
I feel that Mars which is not a star of
course oh well the eyes so all right
remind me that's that's the symbology
all right all right and how does that
play out for you um with my own uh right
my own eyes um in what sense the
physical eyes um what does Mars
represent for you what does Sirius
represent for you in relation to the
symbol of your physical
eyes well I picked up the two stones the
clear Stone and the the brown stone uh
when I woke up uh the other morning and
uh The Brownstone feels very much like
Martian uh energy in a sense which is
old Orion Energy in some senses oh
old rusty Orion Energy ah and the new
clear serus energy balancing it out
right yes and I uh and also it tied into
the red powder uh monochromic powder
that I had used to make uh you know that
brown that there's that color are you
referring to the idea of rodium or
something else um yeah the red and the
monatomic the red monatomic powder well
there are many red monatomic powders but
is the one you may be most familiar with
probably all right and the association
of the red and Mars that was the
association all right and the making the
brown but anyway I took the uh cuz I
have wanted to PE uh my eyes bring them
back to their natural state and they've
been getting
um less clear both far away and close up
all right and has D dramatically change
well made more of a dramatic shift in
the last uh 3 4 months well no wonder
this Christmas looks different yeah
you're
right and I put the clear Stone on my
right eye yes and I put the groundstone
on my left eye yes and it felt very uh
polarized like it would bring them back
to balance the intentional meditational
energetic Act of perform performing that
ritual can it's not that the stones will
oh no I understand but symbolically what
they represent and what they allow you
to do in terms of going through the
motions can be representative of the
proper state in order to allow yourself
to bring them back into Focus yes right
and then I uh also felt little bear um
energy um and pulled that in and it was
like that was a mixture of cuz he um uh
assisted in my leg um um being healed to
the same and so
um I I'm I I just did this the one time
and uh so I'm playing at that in oh
right thank you does that help you
uh yeah I feel that I'm on the right
track for being able to bring them back
to their natural state is there anything
physically that you see that
uh not at the moment except perhaps the
idea of relaxation further mhm and using
that method that method and you will
discover another that has to do with the
idea of looking at something near and
looking at something far yeah I I know
that because I used to be able to see
far away so well and I used to have to
have glasses for a close up yes and now
again also please at the same time
recognize
recognize recognize
that while generally speaking any
condition is changeable sometimes going
along with the collective consensus of
what happens as you quote unquote get
older also can serve a purpose and
sometimes allowing you to reverse that
sometimes requires that you go with it
for a
while oh therein lies a
clue we will see how clearly you find
it
recognize okay I'll play with that all
right anything else
uh
alabon okay
uh is a
future where where is she in the
timeline with me is she a are we getting
back into labels well no I just um no
but you're asking yeah why well because
she's in another dimensional yes so
reality and I so how would giving you a
timeline reference make sense to you
do you mean in the same way that we give
a timeline reference for being 300 years
in your future yes and in that in she's
in another dimensional reality but then
uh the hybrids uh are going to be coming
into this dimensional reality so um so
where are they in relationship um are
they in a a time frame or they are in a
Timeless frame Timeless frame
yes and in that sense to some degree now
and then so was alabon therefore in some
senses it makes no sense to give you a
pin down time frame okay so when I
living in that Timeless sense is no no
no no they are in the timelessness for a
reason they will come out of the
timelessness to join your time frame
when your time frame has become other
than it is okay all right do you follow
that yeah does that help you yeah I
understand uh one last thing when we um
I have a friend that's making getting
close to the transition from the
physical and uh when we're non physical
when we make that is that that like
333,000 cycles per second okay um that
is the transition point
from
for
for for
she is about 297,000
okay there go okay okay um all right so
then that's the first uh
um asro threshold the first threshold
yes the lower astral threshold is
333,000 cycles per second and everybody
is I mean generally generally speaking
okay yeah I just I thought that but I
just wanted to does that help you that
does thank you thank you number
two good dayar and a you good day hi I
really love you out love to you as well
uh I too had a brain question brain
question yeah all right uh
neurologically kind of challenged lately
it neurologically challenged yeah all
right for years I had is that a
politically correct way of saying you're
insane yeah that works oh all right um
for years I had left-sided migraines and
I had sort of bulging veins on the left
side around my ey only SP it around my
eyes that sort of subsided but when
past when I had my children all right
few years all right and since then which
has been coming up very intensely lately
I just I I get slashes like a like a
little gash almost a black and blue mark
under my left eye and I get a fullness
in my brain that feels almost unbearable
and I get a stinging not real headaches
are not migraines and what to what
degree have you allowed yourself to have
the Endeavor of being
checked uh I just had a general physical
and told my doctor about it and said
it's probably just migrants don't worry
about it I would suggest you check
further and more
deeply okay it is not insurmountable but
I would suggest that it is more specific
and you will find that something can be
done but not if you don't find out what
it
is okay so I would suggest you have a
more thorough
scan
okay okay um I also have a question
about
manifesting yes uh I have
been looking for a house for over a year
looking for a house for one orbit yes
there have been a lot of changes during
that time
and the structure the form the finances
all of that and it just keeps evolving
now that it's stayed at a certain level
and I know exactly what what I'm looking
for for several months yes I get
just I don't I don't know where I'm
getting caught uh in what way do you
believe you are getting caught because I
don't have one yes you do okay I I have
the house that I'm living in now no that
is not what we were referring
to I'm missing it yes I know but it's so
much fun
thanks a
lot office
office office the office for now is your
house and from there will be planted the
seeds of the
dwelling that is it's just amazing when
you constantly say things that I just
know I know you just know that's why I
can say them I need to hear because I am
only reflecting what you know yeah the
office is the house energy but it didn't
come what as you expected yeah and so
you are still insisting on the structure
that you recognize instead of
recognizing what the house is the office
serves more purposes and allows you to
lay a
foundation that will then create the
correct house to be built
thereupon perf yes it is if you let it
be exactly instead of worrying it into
the ground right thank you very much
thank you thank you um I have another
question I I saw an image Salvador do
did a a painting of
Christ uh crucified on a Closs made of
Tess yes which is this haunting image to
me I I I my mind just goes back to it
again and again yes other than the sort
of obvious of of the Christ
Consciousness allowing doorways to open
into other dimensions yes is is there
anything else you'd like to say about
that connection as to why it haunts you
yeah yes you were at the
crucifixion well yes as you think of
these things linearly in what you call
past lies you witnessed
it that's is why I'm taking a channeling
class and it's been very very exciting
and one of
the I get the most interesting things in
the middle of the night the other night
most of you do I I can't recall it
exactly but there was there was a lot of
talk of of the Christ Consciousness and
that that sense of what happened when he
was alive and what Earth was like and um
you know you were there and it's and
it's it's very different than what
biblically it is but you know that too
because you were
there that's why it's so fir hand
Witness
in speaking of these things linearly
right you were
there and if you wish it haunts you
because you still are because all things
are simultaneous and now the leak
through and the bleed through to use a
term from One Life to the
next is being experienced more strongly
by
her as each of you claims your own
Christ Consciousness Buddha nature
Krishna Spirit whatever whatever you
wish to call it it's all the same thing
more of these bleed throughs and
different symbols will have different
and stronger effect upon you as they
become more in the moment and you start
to use the experiences you quote unquote
had then in a manner that lets you know
that in some senses you're still having
them
now but to keep it simple and to put it
linearly you were there and that's one
reason why it has this haunting overlay
for you
MH you perceived and understood though
not completely but energetically in your
heart you perceived and understood the
multiple dimensional doorways that were
unfolding in that particular moment at
that time in what you call your
history and remember because it is
simultaneous The Haunting also comes in
both directions you were haunted then
and what you were haunted by then
was your awareness of being haunted by
it now and what you're being haunted by
now is your awareness of being haunted
by it
then you have created your own self-
sustaining self- looping event you are
haunting
yourself about the
experience not in a negative
way do you follow this logic I do does
this help you yes it does yes it does is
is hear anything
that would be helpful for me to hear
about that lifetime particularly in my
relationship one
moment it is not so much that you had
what would be called a familiar
relationship with that entity but you
were very aware of what was going
on and it pierced your
heart strongly do you understand
now we are allowed to give you
[Applause]
this the sun you have now was the sun
you had then and the sun was affected by
the
Sun as you call these terms do you
understand what we are saying to
you you and I all of us right now if you
can feel it are suspended in
limbo we are in an eternal moment at the
moment the sun you have now was the sun
you had then and the sun was affected by
the
sun do you understand what I am say
thank
you the very quick
number
three and are you good day uh I would
like for your comments on a uh kind of
Statistics that has come up now a
statistic yes and it is that there is a
new culture that Now commands uh 1/4 of
the population of this country so it is
said a new culture that commands one
quarter of the population of the country
of of the United States right can you be
more specific about what you mean by
those esoteric terminology okay uh there
about uh well it came comes out
statistically anyway there are three
cultures uh defined as cultures are
belief systems and kind of a mass part
of the mass Consciousness that is uh
existent uh in the country uh one of
them being uh you might say the
Heartland culture which is a people kind
of dating back to before the year 1500
yes then there's the modern culture
which is
from uh from 1500 to now oh based there
namely U no not much care for the
environment yes looking at the self and
and uh and kind of let the rich get
richer and so forth and so okay and then
then there's a modern culture now I mean
a I guess they call it the creative
Consciousness culture all right and that
is uh stemming from the 60s understood
okay now constituting about 1/4 of the
of the population yes and so and uh and
it pro okay uh your comments on uh is
not the uh appearance of these indigo
children now the centuries one born in
the century with the kind of new uh the
new culture uh well they would be an
extension of modern in other words they
are not as we have said many times the
children being born on your planet now
are not an extension of the same species
they are a different species and Ergo a
different culture there are connections
to all the cultures that have existed on
your planet but they are their own
culture that is one of the way
why and how the chains will be broken
they will not be capable of
relating in certain important ways to
the lines and momentum of the old
cultures it will make no sense it will
not
translate they are a different culture
they are a different species so many
people remark that the Indigo kids
really don't fit I just said that yeah
right right and that that kind of
reinforces that but uh at the same time
we can see that there part of the the
movement towards they are certainly the
momentum of the collective Consciousness
in combination yes they are the natural
result of where your Collective Society
is heading yes but to bring it down to
the idea of physical personification and
speaking in terms of physical cultures
they are unique
I was really looking at it in terms of
uh the transformation here that is
really centered around right now around
this new creative Consciousness uh
culture yes okay and you see they they
will really add to the momentum that
we're getting they are the momentum
itself that's one of the things that
makes them so different they are no
longer as separate from the momentum
they are the momentum themselves and
they know
this because remember as we have said
one of the things that allows a
transition to occur for example the idea
of the transition from third density to
Fourth density is knowing that you are
the reality itself that you used to
believe you existed within they know
this they know they are the reality it's
not something they live in it is
something that they are it is
inseparable from them
so those of us which are uh right now
say the ones the kind of the center of
that n that new creative Consciousness
uh culture uh we kind of opened the gate
for them then many of you did yeah yeah
by uh by ourselves going yes into that
and uh yes and then that brought them in
and then they're there now it is in that
sense like a step ladder one rung higher
each time although in many cases the
rungs might also be geometric and
logarithmic in their Ascension because
once you reach a critical MTH threshold
you can go much farther much faster than
simple additional steps can be great
leaps as you say Quantum leaps and in
this now it is again no accident that
your scientists have now begun to
understand the idea of quantum
teleportation so now we would best uh it
would behoove us to be really very
supportive of these young kids you it is
one of the most critical things you can
do because again the idea that every
being now needs to be as possibly fully
supported as they can be to know that
the power is within them that they are
unconditionally loved that they can
create whatever reality they desire
without having to hurt themselves or
hurt anyone else or be hurt in order to
accomplish that it is one of the most
critical things that now can happen on
your planet to break the chain to break
the cycle to break the sequence and to
allow the new culture to exist as a new
culture that can actually in many ways
start from zero from scratch from rest
while simultaneously and paradoxically
utilizing the momentum that brought them
to this point that is one of the most
important things that can occur as we
have said for years years on your planet
that is one of the most important
differences that will ever be made
and it is because it is such a Quantum
break it is because they are such a
truly different culture it is because of
that that no one has guessed the way
it's going to
happen the way the changes will occur
because you don't have the reference
point for it because it's another
reality perspective all
together you had best love them even
more without a shadow of a
DI at this timing we will extend to each
and every one of you once again again
our deep and heartfelt appreciation for
allowing this link this bridge this
transmission to occur through this
Gateway at this time in the spirit of
your own culture we wish you
unconditional holiday spirit and love
and remind you that each and every one
of you are your own holy day every day
every moment you are sacred live that
way love yourselves you are already l
loved unconditionally by the
infinite our love to you as well and
good
day how did it go